

Darshan Patel Director & Country Manager

darshan4742@gmail.com

+91 9586828676

Ahmedabad, India

linkedin.com/in/darshan-infomize in

darshan4742@live.com

An independent and self-motivated Entrepreneur having more than 10 years of experience in the IT industry. Involved in core management, organization & people growth strategies, decision making, product roadmap & deliveries. 8 years of product management experience utilizing to turn ideas into reality. A confident mentor establishing rapport quickly and conducts the training sessions with clarity and enthusiasm.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Director, Country Manager, Scrum MasterInfomize Technologies / HubBroker Aps ☑

04/2015 - Present Ahmedabad, India

B2B, EDI, e-Procurement, e-Commerce, Integration, ERP

Key Result Areas

- Management: Budget AtoZ, Strategic planning, Decision making.
- People: Organization and People Growth, Mentoring, Talent acquisition & promotion.
- **Customers:** Customer engagement, Onboarding, Deliveries, Support process.
- Product: Product roadmap, Sprint planning, Agile execution, Deployments, and Launching.

Sr. Software Developer MSP Concepts Pvt. Ltd. &

MSP Concepts Pvt. Ltd. &

03/2014 - 03/2015 Ahmedabad, India

MSP Concepts is a leading IT Solutions and Services provider based in UK, USA with a development centre in India

- Skills & Responsibilities
- Skills: ASP.NET MVC, .NET Core, Sharepoint, CRM Dynamics, Office 365,
 VB.NET, C#, Entity Framework, Kendo UI, MS SQL, Web API, WPF, WCF.
- Responsibilities: Team leader, Software development, Unit testing, Customer interaction, bug fixing, etc.

Software Developer

AMNEX INFOTECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD. &

03/2012 - 02/2014 Ahmedabad, India

Amnex is a future-first solutions enterprise committed to solving real-world challenges across high-impact sectors

- Technologies & Domains
- Skills: ASP.NET MVC, Office 365, VB.NET, C#, Entity Framework, MS SQL, Web API, WPF, WCF, etc.
- Domain: GPS, GIS, RFID.
- Responsibilities: Software development, Unit testing, Customer interaction, bug fixing, etc.

SKILLS

Entrepreneurship

Organizational Goals Leadership

Team Growth Research

Roadmap vs Deliveries

Budget and Finance

Product Management Analytical

EDI PEPPOL B2B ERP

SOFT SKILLS

Active Listener Disciplined

Transparent Positive Mindset

Curious Fellow Risk Taker

Creative Abstract Thinking

INTERESTS

Photography Travelling

Adventures Mountaineering

Mentoring Books

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) Information Technologies

Sardar Patel University

2007 - 2011

LANGUAGES







ENGLISH

HINDI

GUJARATI